Sezgin Aslantaş

Frontend Developer



Work Experience



Web Developer BRT

(April 2022 to Now)

I undertook the management of the web site design and coding works of Turkey's largest prefabricated pool and pool materials manufacturer. I did both the interface and management panel coding of the company on my own.

Programming languages I used: Html5, Css3, Javascript, Jquery (PDO)

Contact Info

LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/aslantasezgin

- github: aslantasezgin
- +90 531 564 06 32
- aslantasezginn@gmail.com



Junior Frontend Developer Global Medya

(February 2021 to March 2022)

Global Medya was a web agency company that prioritized customer service. I was working as a junior frontend developer in this company. I was communicating with customers, designing and coding their websites according to their requests. Programming Languages I used: Html5, Css3, Javascript, Jquery

Relevant Skills

- Html5
- Css3
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Jquery
- React
- PHP
- MySQL
- NPM
- GIT



Web Developer and Digital Marketing Specialist Turkmahall

(October 2020 to February 2021)
I designed and coded the interface and management panel of the company's website. I did SEO & SEM studies to make it stand out in Digital Media.

About Me

I am 22 years old. I love design and software. I have been continuing to develop myself in the field of software for 2 years. I have had experience working in different software areas. I have worked in both digital marketing, backend and frontend areas. I have been actively developing myself in the frontend area for the last 1 year.

The technologies I know are: Html5, Css3, Javascript, Jquery, PHP, React, Bootstrap, NPM, GIT

Education History



Web Design

Institution: Handan Hayrettin Technical High

School

Year of Graduation: 2018

Computer Programming



Institution: Sakarya University

Year of Graduation: 2020

Contact Info

LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/aslantasezgin

- github: aslantasezgin
- +90 531 564 06 32
- aslantasezginn@gmail.com

Certificates



Flutter Camp

Institution: Piri Reis University

2021



Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Institution: Google

2020